audionetwork.com 2015-05-31

# Privacy Policy - Audio Network - Listen, buy and download today

**Data Protection Information**

[ **www.audionetwork.com**]() is owned and operated by **Audio Network Limited**.

Audio Network Limited and its subsidiary companies **Audio Network US Inc** , **Audio Network Australia Pty Ltd** , **Audio Network Canada Inc,**   **Audio Network (Holland) BV** and **Audio Network GmbH** maintain a strict customer information privacy policy to protect any personal information that you may give us.

We recognize that the growth of internet services, has created additional privacy concerns. We take these concerns very seriously. 

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully - it will help you understand what happens to any personal data that you give us.

* * *

**  
Information we collect from You**

When you register online or order a product or service online, by telephone, fax or post, or email or telephone us with a query, we collect personal data about you directly (including your name, address, telephone and email address).

**Credit Card Information**

When you pay for a product or service online your credit card details are processed over a secure internet site by our third party payment provider **Sage Pay** , an associate of **Elavon Merchant Services**.

As all online payments are processed by Sage Pay on our behalf your credit card details are not visible to anyone from Audio Network Limited nor its subsidiary company.

**AboutCookies**

This website uses Google Analytics and other measurement tools to help analyse how users use the site. These tools use 'cookies', which are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This data is entirely anonymous. Cookies cannot be used to get data from your hard drive, get your e-mail address or personally identifiable information about you.

**What Happens to my Personal Data?**

We use the personal data that you provide directly to administer your www.audionetwork.com account, to supply you with the products and services you choose and to maintain records of your access to, and use of, online services.

If you are based outside the United Kingdom your personal information may be forwarded to our local agent or representative.

We do not pass your personal information on to third parties other than our local agent or representative.

By registering online, buying products or by submitting your details for other purposes you consent to the collection and processing of your personal data as described above. If you have any queries regarding our use of your personal data then please contact [**office@audionetwork.com**](mailto:office@audionetwork.com)

**Will I be Contacted?**

From time to time we may contact you with information relating to our goods and services.

Please note that you can stop receiving this information at any time by either amending your account details online or by contacting [**office@audionetwork.com**](mailto:office@audionetwork.com)

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Occasionally it may be necessary for us to make changes or alterations to this Privacy Policy.

You are advised that it is your responsibility to check  **www.audionetwork.com** for such changes.

Your order is covered by the **Privacy Policy** in force at the time you make your order.
